<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<suppressions xmlns="https://jeremylong.github.io/DependencyCheck/dependency-suppression.1.3.xsd">
<suppress>
   <notes><![CDATA[
IBM MQ 8.0.0.0 through 8.0.0.10, 9.0.0.0 through 9.0.0.5, and 9.1.0.0 through 9.1.1 is vulnerable to a denial of service attack within the TLS key renegotiation function. IBM X-Force ID: 156564.
IBM MQ 8.0.0.4 - 8.0.0.12, 9.0.0.0 - 9.0.0.6, 9.1.0.0 - 9.1.0.2, and 9.1.0 - 9.1.2 AMQP Listeners could allow an unauthorized user to conduct a session fixation attack due to clients not being disconnected as they should. IBM X-Force ID: 159352.
IBM WebSphere MQ V7.1, 7.5, IBM MQ V8, IBM MQ V9.0LTS, IBM MQ V9.1 LTS, and IBM MQ V9.1 CD are vulnerable to a denial of service attack caused by specially crafted messages. IBM X-Force ID: 160013.
IBM MQ 7.5.0.0 - 7.5.0.9, 7.1.0.0 - 7.1.0.9, 8.0.0.0 - 8.0.0.12, 9.0.0.0 - 9.0.0.6, 9.1.0.0 - 9.1.0.2, and 9.1.0 - 9.1.2 command server is vulnerable to a denial of service attack caused by an authenticated and authorized user using specially crafted PCF messages. IBM X-Force ID: 162084.
IBM MQ and IBM MQ Appliance 8.0 and 9.0 LTS could allow a remote attacker with intimate knowledge of the server to cause a denial of service when receiving data on the channel. IBM X-Force ID: 166629.
IBM MQ and IBM MQ Appliance 8.0 and 9.0 LTS client connecting to a Queue Manager could cause a SIGSEGV denial of service caused by converting an invalid message. IBM X-Force ID: 168639.
IBM MQ and IBM MQ Appliance 7.1, 7.5, 8.0, 9.0 LTS, 9.1 LTS, and 9.1 CD could allow a local attacker to obtain sensitive information by inclusion of sensitive data within trace. IBM X-Force ID: 168862.
IBM MQ and IBM MQ Appliance 7.1, 7.5, 8.0, 9.0 LTS, 9.1 LTS, and 9.1 CD is vulnerable to a denial of service attack that would allow an authenticated user to crash the queue and require a restart due to an error processing error messages. IBM X-Force ID: 170967.
IBM MQ and IBM MQ Appliance 7.1, 7.5, 8.0, 9.0 LTS, 9.1 LTS, and 9.1 CD could allow a local attacker to obtain sensitive information by inclusion of sensitive data within runmqras data.
IBM MQ and MQ Appliance 8.0, 9.1 LTS, and 9.1 CD could allow an authenticated user cause a denial of service due to a memory leak. IBM X-Force ID: 175840.

Since the jar is optional; this is supplied by the user. so we don't physically care about the CVE for build purposes.
   ]]></notes>
   <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/com\.ibm/allclient@.*$</packageUrl>
   <cve>CVE-2019-4055</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2019-4227</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2019-4261</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2019-4378</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2019-4568</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2019-4614</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2019-4619</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2019-4656</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2019-4719</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2020-4267</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2020-4310</cve>
   <cve>CVE-2020-4320</cve>
</suppress>
<suppress>
    <notes><![CDATA[
 file name: json-20201115.jar
 CVE-2022-45688 in org.json/json - misleading CPE
 The cpe on the NIST site: cpe:2.3:a:hutool:hutool:5.8.10:*:*:*:*:*:*:* does not seem related to org.json/json
 https://github.com/jeremylong/DependencyCheck/issues/5401
 users can already have some control by setting the -Xss JVM option
 ]]></notes>
    <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/org.json/json@.*$</packageUrl>
    <cve>CVE-2022-45688</cve>
    <cpe>cpe:/a:hutool:hutool</cpe>
  </suppress>    
</suppressions>
